let's go over how you can invert the
让我们来看看如何反转
colors of an object using inkscape on my
在我的上使用Inkscape的对象的颜色
screen here I have this example design
这里的屏幕我有这个样例设计
that I downloaded that consists of a
我下载的内容包括一个
grouping of vector objects for this
为此，对矢量对象进行分组
demonstration I'm going to create a
演示我将创建一个
duplicate of this design here by
通过以下方式复制此设计
pressing Ctrl D and I'm going to move
按下Ctrl D，我就可以移动了
this over to the right here just so I
这个放在右边，这样我就可以
have something to compare the end result
有没有东西可以比较最终的结果
to
至
so when you invert the colors of objects
所以当你反转物体的颜色时
what happens is you're taking a color
发生的情况是，你拿的是一种颜色
and swapping it out with the color that
把它换成那种颜色
opposes it on the color wheel
在色轮上反对它
so every instance of blue will become
所以每一个蓝色的例子都会变成
orange orange will become blue yellow
橙色的橙色将变成蓝黄色
will become purple so on and so forth
会变成紫色，诸如此类
so to accomplish this in inkscape the
因此，要在Inkscape中实现这一点，
first thing you'll want to do is select
您要做的第一件事是选择
your object or objects you can use
您可以使用的一个或多个对象
multiple objects if you'd like and with
如果您愿意，可以使用多个对象
them selected come up here to where it
他们被选中了，来到了这里
says filters
说过滤器
go to color and select invert
转到颜色并选择反转
and once you do that you will get this
一旦你这样做了，你就会得到这个
invert menu with some settings that you
使用您的某些设置倒置菜单
can apply
可以申请
so the first thing we'll want to do is
所以我们要做的第一件事是
turn on the live preview so we can see
打开实时预览，以便我们可以看到
the changes as they're happening and if
正在发生的变化，如果
you look just above that you'll see
你往上看，你就会看到
these three options right here the first
这三个选项是第一个
one is invert Hue if I select that and
一个是反转色调，如果我选择该选项并
inverts all of the colors as you can see
反转您所看到的所有颜色
there but if you notice the eyes which
但如果你注意到那双眼睛
are white or lighter in color they don't
是白色或更浅的颜色，他们不
change they remain a light shade this is
改变他们仍然是一个浅色阴影这是
because we don't have invert lightness
因为我们没有反转的亮度
selected so if I if I select invert
已选择，所以如果我选择了反转
lightness
轻盈
it inverts the lighter tones as well so
它还反转了较浅的色调，因此
that you get more of this photo negative
你会得到更多的照片底片
effect and then finally down here what
效果，然后最后在这里什么
invert transparency does is you won't
反转透明度所做的是你不会
see it on this example but if you're
在本例中可以看到，但是如果您
working with the graphic that has areas
使用包含区域的图形
of partial transparency it'll just
它的部分透明性只会
invert that so for example if it's 80
将其倒置，例如，如果是80
opaque it'll become 20 opaque
它会变得不透明
so let me undo this
所以让我来解开这一切
let me undo the invert lightness because
让我取消反转的亮度，因为
I think for this demonstration it looks
我认为这个演示看起来像是
better like that and if you come up here
这样更好，如果你到这里来
we have this light transparency slider
我们有这个灯光透明度滑块
which allows you to add lightness to the
这使您可以为
design if necessary
必要时进行设计
this can be useful sometimes because
这有时会很有用，因为
when you invert colors sometimes you get
当你反转颜色时，有时你会得到
really dark results this can help you
真的很黑暗的结果这可以帮助你
lighten things up a bit this example
这个例子让事情变得轻松一些
looks good with it not applied so I'm
不涂的话看起来不错，所以我
going to keep it down to zero and then
把它降到零，然后
finally up here you can choose to invert
最后，在这里，您可以选择反转
colors by the channels so by default we
通道的颜色，因此默认情况下我们
have no inversion but if I invert by the
没有倒置，但如果我按
red and blue Channel
红色和蓝色通道
you get this effect right here and if I
你就在这里得到这个效果，如果我
toggle the hue
切换色调
you can see we end up with that effect
你可以看到我们最终会有这样的效果
right there
就在那里
so let's try and invert by the red and
所以让我们试着用红色和
green channels now we get something like
绿色通道现在我们得到的东西是
that
那
and without the Hue applied
并且没有应用色调
it looks like that
看起来是这样的
and then finally we have green and blue
最后我们得到了绿色和蓝色
that looks like that and without the Hue
看起来就是这样，没有色调
you end up with something like that
你最终会得到这样的结果
right there so that's something you
就在那里，所以这就是你的东西
could play around with we can get all of
可以玩耍，我们可以得到所有的
these different results here just like
这些不同的结果就像
that so I liked my results best with no
所以我最喜欢我的结果，没有
inversion like that and I'm going to
像这样的倒置，我要
click apply
单击应用
and then I click close
然后我点击关闭
and there you go that is how you can
就这样，这就是你可以
invert the colors of an object using
使用反转对象的颜色
inkscape now one last thing I'd like to
Inkscape现在我想要做的最后一件事
point out before I end this video is
在我结束这段视频之前要指出的是
that when you apply this filter you're
当你使用这个过滤器时，你是
not actually changing the colors of the
而不是实际更改
objects you're just changing the color
您只是更改了颜色的对象
of their appearance on your screen now
他们现在出现在你的屏幕上
if I click on this object right here
如果我点击这里的这个物体
this right here is the inverted copy and
这是反转的副本，
this over here is the original copy with
这是原件，上面有
this object selected you can see here
您可以在此处看到所选的对象
this is a light shade of lavender but if
这是淡紫色，但如果
you look down here in the color status
你在颜色状态下往下看
bar it's still its original color as you
它仍然是原来的颜色，就像你
can see over here that's how it's
可以看到这里，就是这样
registering because this is just a
注册，因为这只是
temporary filter that's applied to the
临时筛选器应用于
object
对象
now if you're going to be taking your
现在，如果你要带着你的
design and exporting it as a JPEG or a
设计并将其导出为JPEG或
PNG then you can ignore this part of the
PNG然后您可以忽略这部分
video because this doesn't really apply
视频，因为这并不真正适用于
here but if you're going to take the SVG
在这里，但如果你要乘坐SVG
file and try to open it in another
文件并尝试在另一个文件中打开它
application such as qriket design space
Qriket设计空间等应用
or illustrator this effect is not going
或插图画家这种效果是不会
to carry over because this is an
继续下去，因为这是
inkscape specific effect you're going to
您将使用Inkscape特定效果
end up with this right here
就在这里结束
so if you truly want your colors to be
所以如果你真的想让你的颜色
inverted what you'll want to do is take
相反，你想要做的是
an original copy and swap out and change
一份原件，换出和更改
the colors manually one by one so if I
手动逐一配色，所以如果我
select this object I can come over here
选择这个对象我可以到这里来
to my dropper tool and select that area
到我的滴管工具，然后选择该区域
and now it is the desired color as you
现在它是你想要的颜色
can see there
在那里可以看到
so I'll do the same thing I'm going to
所以我会做我要做的事情
click on the nose now and do the same
现在点击鼻子，然后做同样的事情
thing I'm just going to use the keyboard
我只想用键盘
shortcuts to toggle between the tools
在工具之间切换的快捷键
for the dropper the keyboard shortcut is
对于拖放器，键盘快捷键为
d
D
and I'll click on that and then I'll
我会点击它，然后我会
switch back to the selection tool which
切换回选择工具，该工具
is s and I'll do the same thing over
是不是S和我会重蹈覆辙
here switch back and forth between D and
这里在D和D之间来回切换
S
S
and you could just go through here one
你可以从这里走一趟
by one and change all of these colors
然后改变所有这些颜色
like that
就像这样
and there you go now we have a copy that
好了，现在我们有一个副本，
has colors that are truly inverted and
具有真正反转的颜色和
then we have this filtered copy over
然后我们把这份经过过滤的复印件
here now if you want to remove the
现在，如果您要删除
filter at any time you could just select
您可以随时选择筛选器
the objects and come up here to where it
然后把这些东西放到这里来
says filters and go down to where it
表示过滤器并向下到它所在的位置
says remove filters and now it's back to
说移除过滤器，现在它又回到了
how it was previously
它以前是什么样子
so that's how you can work with color
这就是你处理颜色的方法
inversion in inkscape if you found this
Inkscape中的倒置如果你发现了这个
lesson useful then consider checking out
有用的一课，那就考虑退房吧
my inkscape master class it's a
我的Inkscape大师班是一个
collection of over 60 videos where I go
收集了60多个视频，我去了哪里
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and I explain what they are and
inkscape和我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work kind of like
演示它们的工作原理有点像
how I did in this video we even have a
我在这个视频中的表现我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以询问
questions and get help from me anytime
随时向我提问并寻求帮助
you want and best of all there's no
你想要的，最重要的是没有
monthly membership fees you just pay 17
每月只需支付17美元会员费
one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次，你就会终身监禁我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]